<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working Title</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Working Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 15:04:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>#AgainstTrump</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/post/againsttrump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 15:04:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/post/againsttrump/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t expect too many people to read this, that&amp;rsquo;s not important.  What&amp;rsquo;s important is that, years from now, I have a place to point to and prove that I was always, &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt;, against Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Democrats, this won&amp;rsquo;t be so remarkable.  It&amp;rsquo;s assumed that a Democrat is against Trump, so no matter what their private feelings they will always have the flexibility to assert moral authority.  &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Oh yes, I remember &amp;ndash; what a dark time that was.  It just goes to show you how we really weren&amp;rsquo;t ready for Obama &amp;ndash; yes, I do think it was racial.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; And so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for a conservative Republican who intends to remain conservative (at least), it&amp;rsquo;s going to be valuable to say &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;No.  Don&amp;rsquo;t put that on me.  I never flirted with the guy, I was firmly against him from the get-go.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; If you don&amp;rsquo;t say it now, no one will believe you later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will always be Trump apologists, but they will be rarer and rarer as the years roll on.  But depending on what happens in the weeks and months ahead, there will be revisionists:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If Trump loses the nomination:&lt;/strong&gt; A great many conservatives will say &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;See?  Trump brought something to the race.  Isn&amp;rsquo;t it fantastic that he brought people to the party, and paved the way for a real conservative?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll say: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Nice try, but you carried his water and now you lost.  You have no credibility.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If Trump wins the nomination:&lt;/strong&gt; About one day later he move so quickly to the center-left that every half-wit talk show host will start calling him a Judas and blaming the &amp;ldquo;establishment&amp;rdquo; for propping him up.  He will be the next chapter in a long saga of betrayal.  When he loses to Clinton, the narrative will be &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;we always lose when we nominate a squish!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll say: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Where were you when it was abundantly clear that he lacked no principles or fortitude?  I remember: you argued that he was an &amp;lsquo;insurgent candidate&amp;rsquo; who was &amp;lsquo;energizing conservatives&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;disrupting the establishment.&amp;rsquo;  The establishment didn&amp;rsquo;t create him; you did.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here, I&amp;rsquo;m saying it: I oppose Donald Trump.  I&amp;rsquo;ll oppose him if he&amp;rsquo;s the nominee, I&amp;rsquo;ll oppose him if he&amp;rsquo;s the president.  I&amp;rsquo;ll actively vote against him each time I can.  I will not be a member of any party in which he holds a leadership position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks, that feels better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>